(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
おめかし中...
Getting dressed...
扉開けば
If I open the door
捻れた昼の夜
A twisted daytime night
昨日どうやって帰った
How I got home yesterday
体だけが確か
Only my body is certain
おはよう これから
Good morning, from now on
また迷子の続き
Continuing to be a lost child again
見慣れた知らない
A familiar, unknown
景色の中で
scenery within
Hello, world!
もうダメって思ってから
Since I thought it was no use
わりと何だかやれている
I've somehow been managing
死にきらないくらいに丈夫
Sturdy enough not to die
何かちょっと恥ずかしい
It's a bit embarrassing
やるべきことは
The things I should do
忘れていても解る
I understand even if I've forgotten
そうしないととても
Because if I don't, it's very
苦しいから
painful
顔を上げて
Lift your head
黒い目の人
Person with black eyes
君が見たから
Because you looked
光は生まれた
the light was born
選んだ色で塗った
Painted with chosen colors
世界に囲まれて
Surrounded by the world
選べない傷の意味は
The meaning of wounds I couldn't choose
どこだろう
where is it?
ご自分だけがヒーロー
You're your own hero
世界の真ん中で
In the center of the world
終わるまで出っ張り
Sticking out until it ends
ステージの上
On top of the stage
どうしよう
What should I do?
空っぽのふりも出来ない
I can't even pretend to be empty
ハローどうも僕はここ
Hello, hi, I am here
覚えてしまった感覚
A sensation I've remembered
思い出とは違う類
Different from a memory
もっと涙の側にあって
Being closer to tears
いつも心臓掴まれていて
With my heart always being gripped
充分理解出来ている
I understand it well enough
ずっとそれと一緒に
Being with it forever
そうじゃないと何も
Because otherwise, I can't
見えないから
see anything
息を繋ぐ
Linking breaths
生きる強い人
A strong person who lives
止まる心を
The heart that stops
引き摺って連れてきた
Dragging it along
塞いだ耳で聴いた
Heard with blocked ears
虹の様なメロディー
A melody like a rainbow
砕けない思いが
Unbreakable feelings
内側で歌う
singing inside
隠れていたってヒーロー
A hero even if hidden
守るものがある
There's something to protect
恐いのはそれほど
What's scary is that much
気付いているから
because I've noticed
扉開けば
If I open the door
捻れた本当の嘘
A twisted real lie
空っぽのふりのふり
Pretending to pretend to be empty
体だけが確か
Only my body is certain
おはよう 今でも
Good morning, even now
まだ最後の続き
Still the continuation of the end
叫ぼう そこから
Let's shout, from there
ハロー どうも 僕はここ
Hello, how are you? I am here
さあ 目を開けて
Now, open your eyes
君は強い人
You are a strong person
その目が見たから
Because those eyes saw it
全ては生まれた
Everything was born
選んだ色で塗った
Painted with colors I chose
世界に囲まれて
Surrounded by the world
選べない傷の意味はどこだろう
Where is the meaning of the wounds I didn't choose?
ご自分だけがヒーロー
Only you are the hero
守ったものがある
There is something you protected
恐いのはその価値を知っているから
What's scary is that you know its value
塞いだ耳で聴いた
I heard it with blocked ears
虹の様なメロディ
A melody like a rainbow
砕けない思いが内側で歌う
Unbreakable feelings sing from within
悲鳴をあげたヒーロー
The hero who let out a scream
世界の真ん中で
In the middle of the world
終わるまで出ずっぱり自分が観ている
Always on stage until the end, watching myself
だからもう死んだふりも意味ない
So pretending to be dead is meaningless anymore
ハロー どうも 僕はここ
Hello, how are you? I am here
はい！というわけで皆様、こんばんは！こんねね！
Hi! So everyone, good evening! Kon-Nene!
ホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当、アイドルVTuberの桃鈴ねねです！
Hololive Gen 5, orange representative, Idol VTuber Momosuzu Nene here!
イエーイ！みんな元気？ヤッホー！んま、んま、んま、んま、んま…
Yay! Is everyone doing well? Yahoo! Mwa mwa mwa...
というわけで、今1曲目、あのBUMP（OF CHICKEN）さんの「Hello,world!」をお聴きいただきました。
So, you just heard the first song, 'Hello,world!' by BUMP OF CHICKEN.
ちょっとだけ緊張しちゃったな。はぁ〜。
I was a bit nervous. Phew.
ちょっと音量調節します。
I'll adjust the volume a bit.
はい、というわけで本日…あ、本日じゃないね。8月に2周年を迎えまして…
So today... well, not today. I reached my 2nd anniversary in August...
えっ…ちょっと遅れちゃったんですけど、10月になっちゃったんですけど、今日2周年のお祝いさせていだだきます。
Well... it's a bit late, it's already October, but I'll be celebrating my 2nd anniversary today.
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
今日のハッシュタグはこちらです！#桃鈴ねね2周年、そのままな。
Today's hashtag is this! #桃鈴ねね2周年, just like that.
そのままでいっぱいツイートしてください。ねっ子じゃない人も、今日くらいツイートいかがですか？
Please tweet a lot with it. Even if you're not a Nekko, how about a tweet just for today?
たまにはいいでしょう！フフッ。
Once in a while is fine, right? Hehe.
精一杯してくださいね。スクショいっぱい撮ってください。
Give it your all! Take lots of screenshots.
ねね動くからちょっとスクショの難易度が高いと思うけど、みんなならできるよね？
Nene moves around, so screenshots might be tough, but you guys can do it, right?
プロのスクショリストならできるはずなんで、撮れるもんなら撮ってみてください。
Professional screenshot-ists should be able to, so try taking some if you can.
はい、というわけで、あの、ちょっと休憩いいかな？疲れちゃったよ。
Okay, can I take a little break? I'm already tired.
ちょっと水分補給して。はぁ〜。
Gotta hydrate. Phew.
いやなんか、あの、ステージに、あの、こうやって立つの久しぶりな気がします。
I feel like it's been a while since I stood on a stage like this.
見てくださいステージ！可愛いでしょ！
Look at the stage! Isn't it cute?
ねねのねっ子の時の衣装の、耳がついてて。ねねの頭のお花もついてて、超可愛いんだから。
It's based on Nene's Nekko outfit, with the ears. It's also got Nene's hair flowers, it's so cute.
さてさてさて、次に行く前に、今ねちょっと1曲目から本気出しすぎちゃって、あの、暑いのね。上着を脱いでいきたいと思います。
Now then, before we move on, I went too hard on the first song and I'm hot. I'm going to take off my jacket.
ちょっとね、上着を脱ぐだけとはいえ、女の子の生着替えを見せるわけにはいきませんので、少しだけ皆さんお待ちください。
Even though I'm just taking off my jacket, I can't show a girl changing live, so please wait a moment.
それじゃあ。上着…パッ！
Alright then. Jacket... off!
ほら〜！じゃーん！
Look! Ta-da!
やーん！見ないで！生肌見ないでください！やめてください！
Ah! Don't look! Don't look at my bare skin! Please stop it!
はい、というわけで、あの、次の曲。まだ始まったばっかりですので、みんなガンガン行こうぜ！
Okay, so, the next song. It's just getting started, so let's go all out, everyone!
というわけで、次の曲いっちゃおうかな。
So, let's head to the next song.
音大丈夫かな？心配だけど。ま、いっか。
I wonder if the sound is okay? I'm worried, but... oh well.
というわけで次の曲いってみましょう！それでは、2曲目聴いてください。「セカイ」。
So let's go to the next song! Please listen to the second song, 'Sekai'.
ずっと探してたんだよ
I've been searching for it all this time
特別だって言える場所
A place I can call special
なんで僕を選んだの
Why did you choose me?
笑うキミが手を引いたんだ
You smiled and pulled my hand
だってキミはすごいから
Because you're so amazing
負けらんないなって思うんだよ
I feel like I can't afford to lose
どんな時も僕の中に
No matter the time, inside of me
キミの声が鳴り響いていた
Your voice was resonating
怖いんだ 何もない僕だけどできるかな
I'm scared. I have nothing, but can I do it?
自信のなさとしようもなさでいい勝負さ
It's a close match between my lack of confidence and helplessness
けどキミは「それがどうしたの？」って顔をして
But you look at me as if to say "So what?"
歌を歌うじゃない それはズルいじゃない
And you start singing. That's not fair.
飛び込んでいこう 僕らのセカイへ
Let's dive into our world
正解の想いに出会えるかな
I wonder if I can meet the correct feelings
歌っていたい 踊っていたい
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing
痛いくらい笑えるように
So I can smile until it hurts
名前もない 僕らの世界を
Our world, which doesn't even have a name
迷っていけるよ キミとだから
I can keep wandering, because I'm with you
変わっていこう 願うように
Let's keep changing, just as we wished
今僕ら 期待の未体験を
Now we are experiencing the expected unexpected
キミの未来を僕が歌うよ
I'll sing of your future
描いてもっと Yeah
Draw it more, yeah
泣いてもいいじゃん それも答えだ
It's okay to cry, that's an answer too
どうしたっていいよ 想いは全部
It doesn't matter what happens, all these feelings
零さぬように抱き締めながら
I'll hold them tight so they don't spill over
キミと見たいセカイへ
Towards the world I want to see with you
ずっと探してたんだよ
I've been searching for it all this time
特別だって言える場所
A place I can call special
どんな僕になるんだろう
What kind of person will I become?
踊るココロ変えないように
So that my dancing heart doesn't change
ちょっとだけのその先で
Just a little bit further ahead
また笑えるよ
I'll be able to smile again
もらったバトンは勇気に
The baton I received becomes courage
ありがとうは歌声に
My gratitude becomes my singing voice
気付いたんだ 僕にしか出来ないこともあること
I realized there are things only I can do
誰かのとこへちゃんと歌を届けたいのさ
I want to deliver my song properly to someone
ほら 怖くて震える手でビート刻めば
Look, if I keep the beat with my trembling, scared hands
夢も近いじゃない 僕らひとりじゃない
My dream isn't far, is it? We are not alone.
飛び込んでいこう 僕らのセカイへ
Let's dive into our world
正解の想いに出会えるかな
I wonder if I can meet the correct feelings
歌っていたい 踊っていたい
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing
痛いくらい笑えるように
So I can smile until it hurts
名前もない 僕らの世界を
Our world, which doesn't even have a name
迷っていけるよ キミとだから
I can keep wandering, because I'm with you
変わっていこう 願うように
Let's keep changing, just as we wished
今僕ら 期待の未体験を
Now we are experiencing the expected unexpected
飛び込んでいこう 僕らのセカイへ
Let's dive into our world
正解の想いに出会えるかな
I wonder if I can meet the correct feelings
歌っていたい 踊っていたい
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing
痛いくらい笑えるように
So I can smile until it hurts
名前もない 僕らの世界を
Our world, which doesn't even have a name
迷っていけるよ キミとだから
I can keep wandering, because I'm with you
変わっていこう 願うように
Let's keep changing, just as we wished
今僕ら 期待の未体験を
Now we are experiencing the expected unexpected
キミの未来を僕が歌うよ
I'll sing of your future
描いてもっと Yeah
Draw it more, yeah
泣いてもいいじゃん それも答えだ
It's okay to cry, that's an answer too
どうしたっていいよ 想いは全部
It doesn't matter what happens, all these feelings
零さぬように抱き締めながら
I'll hold them tight so they don't spill over
キミと見たいセカイへ
Towards the world I want to see with you
はーい！
Phew!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ちょっとティッシュ...
Wait, a tissue...
喉、喉、喉かティッシュおくれ
Thirsty, thirsty, I'm thirsty, or give me a tissue.
やばい
Oh no.
鼻水吹き出しちゃった途中で
My nose started running in the middle of it.
ちょっと待ってねみんな。やべ。
Wait a moment, everyone. Oops.
ありがとう
Thank you
よいしょ
Up we go
はい！というわけで2曲目「セカイ」をお聞きいただきました！
Alright! So you just listened to the second song, 'Sekai'!
どうですか？ねね、ここが好きなんだけど、みんなどうかな？
How was it? Nene likes this part, what do you guys think?
ここね！お尻、お尻から見てて、お尻。
This part! My butt, look at it from behind, my butt.
どーよ！どーよこのぷりぷりのお尻！
How's that! How's this bouncy butt of mine!
待たせたなみんなー！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
はーい、というわけで
Okay, so anyway,
ここからはですね皆様、お待たせのゲストパートに行きたいと思います！
From here on, everyone, I'd like to move on to the guest part you've been waiting for!
みんなね、サムネイルでどの先輩が来てくれるか、もうわかっていると思いますが
Everyone, you probably know from the thumbnail which senpai are coming,
一体どのような組み合わせで、どのように歌っているのか
but what kind of combination and how they will sing...
謎は迷宮入りしたので、それを解明しに行きたいと思います！
is a mystery that has entered the labyrinth, so I want to go solve it!
というわけでみんなでね、頑張りましたので、要チェック！
So, everyone together, we did our best, so check it out!
みんな目ん玉ひん剥いて、あの、こうやって画面に目ん玉見せつけて
Everyone, open your eyes wide and show your eyes to the screen like this,
あの、やってください...あ、見てください、コメントもしてください
um, please do it... I mean, please watch and leave comments,
見てますんで！
because I'm watching!
はい、というわけでいってみましょう！それではゲストパート...
Okay, so let's go! Now, the guest part...
スタート！ゴーゴーゴー...！
Start! Go go go...!
アイドル新鋭隊
作詞・作曲 Mitchie M
Idol Shin'eitai
Lyrics & Composition: Mitchie M
More More (Whoo!) More More (Whoo!)
More More (Whoo!) More More!
Jump!! 限界超え
Jump!! Beyond the limit
完全無欠 スターを目指せ
Aim for a perfect star
Jump!! 元気をシェア
Jump!! Share the energy
負けない者の女神よ
The goddess of those who don't lose
ホ・ロ・ライブ 消せぬ夢で結ばれた
Holo-live, Bound by an indelible dream
ホ・ロ・ライブ命
Holo-live life
We are アイドル新鋭隊
We are Idol Shin'eitai
L・O・V・E More More Jump!
L-O-V-E More More Jump!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
落ち込むなんて日常茶飯事
Feeling down is an everyday occurrence
ファイト・ファイト ねねち
Fight, fight, Nenechi
けど速攻笑顔取り戻すわ
But I'll get my smile back in no time
キューティー・スマイル みこち
Cutie smile, Mikochi
一度きりのティーンの 儚い花盛り
A once-in-a-lifetime teen's fleeting peak of bloom
（ハイ！ハイ！）
(Hi! Hi!)
下向いてちゃ人生は損
Life is a waste if you look down
フレッシュ・アイドル イェーイ！
Fresh idol, yay!
事務所の方針なんて無視
Ignore the agency's policy
ツンデレ・ガール あずき
Tsundere girl, AZKi
ビジネスライクで演じるのイヤ
I hate acting business-like
G・U・T・S すばる
G-U-T-S, Subaru
心に嘘つかず
Don't lie to your heart
（ハイ！）
(Hi!)
Spotlight浴び step踏めば
Under the spotlight, if you take a step
（ハイ！）
(Hi!)
駆け上がる道照らされるよ
The road you're running up will be lit
ウー・レッツゴー！
Woo, let's go!
Jump!! 限界超え
Jump!! Beyond the limit
完全無欠 スターを目指せ
Aim for a perfect star
Jump!! 元気をシェア
Jump!! Share the energy
負けない者の女神よ
The goddess of those who don't lose
ホ・ロ・ライブ 消せぬ夢で結ばれた
Holo-live, Bound by an indelible dream
ホ・ロ・ライブ命
Holo-live life
We are アイドル新鋭隊
We are Idol Shin'eitai
L・O・V・E More More Jump!
L-O-V-E More More Jump!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
騒いだ者勝ちの世界でも
Even in a world where the loudest wins
ファイト・ファイト みこち
Fight, fight, Mikochi
清楚可憐はアイドルの pride
Neatness and prettiness is an idol's pride
キューティー・スマイル すばる
Cutie smile, Subaru
チヤホヤされて 満足しちゃわないように
Don't be satisfied just by being pampered
（ハイ！ハイ！）
(Hi! Hi!)
心広く志高く
Keep a broad mind and high aspirations
ピュア・ピュア・ヒロイン イェーイ！
Pure, pure heroine, yay!
仲悪いとか解散とか
Bad relationships or breaking up
ツンデレ・ガール あずき
Tsundere girl, AZKi
フェイク・ニュースに惑わされない
Won't be misled by fake news
G・U・T・S ねねち
G-U-T-S, Nenechi
ハムより薄い女子の 儚い友情だとか
Women's friendships thinner than ham, fleeting as they are
（ハイ！ハイ！）
(Hi! Hi!)
そんな通説覆すパワー
The power to overturn such conventional wisdom
ウー・レッツゴー！
Woo, let's go!
Jump!! 涙を超え
Jump!! Beyond the tears
千載一遇 チャンス掴め
Seize the once-in-a-lifetime chance
Jump!! 波飛び乗り
Jump!! Ride the waves
一世風靡起こそうよ
Let's take the world by storm
ホ・ロ・ライブ スターダムへのセトリ旅したら
Holo-live, If we journey through the setlist to stardom
ホ・ロ・ライブ命
Holo-live life
あなたもアイドル新鋭隊
You too are part of Idol Shin'eitai
L・O・V・E More More Jump!
L-O-V-E More More Jump!
ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi!
ハッピー・ホロライブ！
Happy Hololive!
ラブリー・ホロライブ！
Lovely Hololive!
未来のスーパー・アイドル ここらで一気にドン！
Future super idols, let's go all out here!
闇貫くレーザービームのように 希望の光を放ち続けて
Like a laser beam piercing the darkness, keep emitting the light of hope
ウー・レッツゴー！
Woo, let's go!
Jump!! 限界超え
Jump!! Beyond the limit
完全無欠 スターを目指せ
Aim for a perfect star
Jump!! 元気をシェア
Jump!! Share the energy
負けない者の女神よ
The goddess of those who don't lose
ホ・ロ・ライブ 消せぬ夢で結ばれた
Holo-live, Bound by an indelible dream
ホ・ロ・ライブ命
Holo-live life
ミラクルへGO GO GO!
Go Go Go to the miracle!
エスコート
Escort
一緒に
together
We are アイドル新鋭隊
We are Idol Shin'eitai
L・O・V・E More More Jump!
L-O-V-E More More Jump!
こころぴょんぴょん待ち
My heart is waiting, hop hop!
考えるふりして
I'll pretend to be thinking,
もうちょっと近づいちゃえ
And get a little bit closer!
簡単には教えないっ
I won't tell you that easily!
こんなに好きなことは
The fact that I like you this much
内緒なの
Is a secret.
ふわふわどきどき内緒ですよ
Fluffy, heart-pounding, it's a secret!
はじめがかんじんつーんだつーんだ
The beginning is important, tsun-da tsun-da!
ふわふわどきどき内緒だって
Fluffy, heart-pounding, I said it's a secret!
いたずら笑顔でぴょんぴょん
With a mischievous smile, hop hop!
扉開けたとたん見知らぬ世界へと
The moment I open the door, into an unknown world,
そんなのないよ　ありえない
That can't be, impossible!
それがアリエルかもミルク色の異次元
But it might be possible, a milk-colored alternate dimension!
コーヒーカップ覗いたら
When I peered into my coffee cup,
私が私を見つめてました
I found myself staring back at me.
なんで？なんで？ふたりいる？
Why? Why? Are there two of me?
困りますね　きっとおんなじ趣味
This is troubling, we surely have the same tastes!
誰を見つめるの？君でしょ
Who are you staring at? It's you, right?
君だけ見てるよ　これは夢カップの夢
I'm only looking at you, this is a dream, a cup's dream!
飲みほしておしまい？
Will it end once I drink it all?
いつもぴょんぴょん可能楽しさ求めて
Always able to hop hop, seeking out the fun,
もうちょっとはじけちゃえ
Let's burst out a little more!
一緒なら素敵だーい！
It's wonderful when we're together!
君に言わせたいから（いなさいっ）
Because I want you to say it (Say it!)
こころぴょんぴょん待ち考えるふりして
My heart is waiting, hop hop! I'll pretend to be thinking,
もうちょっと近づいちゃえ
And get a little bit closer!
簡単には教えないっ
I won't tell you that easily!
こんなに好きなことは好きだってことはわ内緒なの
The fact that I like you this much, the fact that I love you... is a secret.
ふわふわどきどき内緒ですよ
Fluffy, heart-pounding, it's a secret!
はじめがかんじんつーんだつーんだ
The beginning is important, tsun-da tsun-da!
ふわふわどきどき内緒だって
Fluffy, heart-pounding, I said it's a secret!
いたずら笑顔でぴょんぴょん
With a mischievous smile, hop hop!
日常のなかにも不思議の交差点
Even in everyday life, there are intersections of wonder!
それならあるね　ありえるん
Well, that could happen, it's possible!
ありえない角度に切り分けたケーキが
The cake sliced at an impossible angle...
さすらいウサギ呼んじゃったよ
It called over a wandering rabbit!
私も私と驚きました
I was surprised too, together with myself!
なんで？なんで？しゃべるウサ？
Why? Why? A talking rabbit?
困りました　ついお茶を飲んで
How troubling, I ended up having some tea!
ついに見つけたよ君への君との運命
I've finally found it, my destiny for you, with you!
いいよね夢恋の夢
Isn't it nice? A dream, a dream of love!
初めてのときめき？
My first time feeling this way?
胸がランラン歌うスキップしながらはにかんで誘ってよ
My heart is singing happily as I skip along, shyly asking you out!
一緒なら無敵だーい！
When we're together, we're invincible!
本音かくせなくなる（本音だ！）
I can't hide my true feelings anymore (It's the truth!)
あしたランラン希望今すぐがいいなはにかんで誘ってよ
Tomorrow's full of happy hopes, but I want it right now, so shyly ask me out!
一瞬だけ耳もとほんとは好きなんだと
Just for a moment, in your ear, 'Actually, I like you'
好きなんだつまりななな囁く
I like you, in other words, na-na-na, I whisper.
これは夢カップの夢
This is a dream, a cup's dream!
飲みほしておねがい！
Drink it all, please!
いつもぴょんぴょん可能楽しさ求めて
Always able to hop hop, seeking out the fun,
もうちょっとはじけちゃえ
Let's burst out a little more!
一緒なら素敵だーい！
It's wonderful when we're together!
君に言わせたいから（言いなさいっ）
Because I want you to say it (Say it!)
こころぴょんぴょん待ち考えるふりして
My heart is waiting, hop hop! I'll pretend to be thinking,
もうちょっと近づいちゃえ
And get a little bit closer!
簡単には教えないっ
I won't tell you that easily!
こんなに好きなことはいいよね夢恋の夢
The fact that I like you this much... isn't a dream of love nice?
好きなんだつまりななな内緒なの
I like you, in other words, na-na-na, it's a secret.
ふわふわどきどき内緒ですよ
Fluffy, heart-pounding, it's a secret!
はじめがかんじんつーんだつーんだ
The beginning is important, tsun-da tsun-da!
ふわふわどきどき内緒だって
Fluffy, heart-pounding, I said it's a secret!
いたずら笑顔でぴょんぴょん
With a mischievous smile, hop hop!
イエーイ！ イエーイ！
Yay! Yay!
Daydream caféをお聴きいただきました。ありがとう！
You just heard "Daydream café". Thank you!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
はぁー、疲れたわ。 めちゃめちゃ疲れたわ。
Haa... I'm tired. I'm so incredibly tired.
え、でも待って。 練習の中でも一番上手くなかった？
Wait, wasn't that the best we've ever done it, even in practice?
ね！ 上手かったー！
Right! It was great!
可愛かった！ミスも含めて可愛かった！
It was cute! Including the mistakes, it was all cute!
というわけで、今回はまつり先輩とはあちゃまに来ていただきましたー！
So, for this song, we had Matsuri-senpai and Haachama join us!
イエーイ！ありがとう！ 2周年おめでとう！
Yay! Thank you! Congratulations on your 2nd anniversary!
ありがとう、ありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
実は、ね、チーム名！
Actually, we have a team name!
そうなんです！ 作っちゃったんだよねー。
That's right! We made one together!
じゃあ、いきますよ。 挨拶あるんで。
Okay, here we go. We have a greeting.
せーの、私たち、ぴかぶ〜！
One, two... We are, Pikabu!
イエーイ！
Yay!
最近決まったもんねー。 そうだね。
We just decided on it recently. Yeah.
めちゃめちゃ必死にチーム名選んだんです。 そういうこととかもね、詳しく話せる機会がどっかであるといいなー。
We worked really hard choosing our team name. I hope we'll have a chance to talk about that in more detail somewhere!
これからもこの3人で…
From now on, the three of us...
いろんなことやりたいんだもん！
I want to do so many things!
やりたいやりたい！
We want to! We want to!
3人だけでね、この...
Just the three of us, you know...
今後もさ、3人の動きに、なんか注目しといてもらえると嬉しいなってな、
going forward, I'd be happy if you could keep an eye on our activities...
てな、てな、てな...
...together, together, together...
なんだよ！なんだよ！
What was that?! What was that?!
もしさ、次ライブがあったとしても呼んでいいの？呼んでいいの？
Even if there's a next live, can I invite you guys again? Can I?
呼んでよ！呼んでよ！
Invite us! Invite us!
どうしようかなーって...
I'll think about it...
呼んでくれるでしょ？聞いてよー。
You'll invite us, right? Listen to us!
いっぱいね、ぜひぜひ。はい、注目しててください。
Please do, many times. Yes, please keep an eye on us.
ダンスだけさ、どうだった？
How was just the dance?
めちゃくちゃ可愛かったでしょ！
It was super cute, right!
はまっちゃう！
I'm hooked!
まつりちゃんはなんかダンスやってるイメージがあったんだけど、
I had an image of Matsuri-chan dancing, but...
はあちゃま誘う時に、なんか「はあちゃまもやれますー」って言うから...
when I invited Haachama, she was like, "Haachama can do it too!"
そんな言い方してないよ！
I didn't say it like that!
言ってたから、「えっ、じゃあはあちゃまも来てくれる？」って言ったら...
She did say that, so when I asked "Oh, then will you come too?", she said...
来ちゃいました。
I came.
快く二つ返事で来てくれた。ありがとう。
She agreed immediately. Thank you.
どこが難しかった？
Which part was difficult?
でも、やっぱ最後の確変みたいな急にさ、ね。
But, like the sudden change at the end, right?
これが急に突然来るとことかね。
Like when this part suddenly comes in.
あと歌詞周りのさ、途中これのあとのぴょんぴょんぴょん。
And the part during the lyrics, after this, the hopping.
めっちゃ気合入れた。
Put a lot of effort into that.
はあちゃまめちゃくちゃ飛んでた。びっくりした。
Haachama was jumping so much. I was surprised.
そこも見てほしいです。
I want people to see that too.
はいということで、ああ疲れちゃいました？
So, are you guys tired?
疲れちゃってない、まだあるでしょ！頑張って！
Not tired, there's more, right! Do your best!
まだまだあるので、この後もお楽しみください。
There's still more to come, so please enjoy the rest.
ということで、締めの挨拶までうちら考えたんだよね。
So, we even thought of a closing greeting.
せーの！
Ready, set...
レッツ！ビーカーンズー！
Let's! Be-Khan-Z!
イエーイ！バイバーイ！
Yay! Bye-bye!
残響散歌 / 作詞：aimerrhythm 作曲：飛内将大
Zankyosanka / Lyrics: aimerrhythm Composition: Masahiro Tobinai
誰が袖に咲く花か
Whose sleeve does this flower bloom on?
ただそこに藍を落とした
Simply dropping indigo right there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night that melts colors flamboyantly
銀朱の月を添えて
Accompanied by a vermilion moon
転がるように風を切って
Slicing through the wind as if rolling
躓くごとに強くなった
Growing stronger with every stumble
光も痛みも怒りも全部
Light, pain, and anger—all of it,
抱きしめて
embrace it.
選ばれなければ
If you aren't chosen,
選べばいい
then just choose.
声を届かせて 夜の向こうへ
Let your voice reach beyond the night.
涙で滲んでた あんなに遠くの景色まで
To that distant scenery blurred by tears,
響き渡れ
let it resonate.
何を奏でて 誰に届けたくて
What to play, who to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's fine to remain uncertain.
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the emotions,
どんなに長い葛藤も
no matter how long the conflict,
歌と共に残響
reverberate along with the song.
ただ一人の千夜
A thousand nights all alone.
違わない対を結べば
If we tie an unerring bond,
派手な色も負かすように
so as to outshine even flamboyant colors,
真紅の香こそあはれ
the deep crimson scent is truly moving.
この先どんな辛い時も
From now on, no matter how tough it gets,
口先よりも胸を張って
puff out your chest rather than just talking,
抱いた夢の灯を全部
and all the lights of the dreams you've held,
辿るだけ
just follow them.
逃げ出すため
It wasn't to run away
ここまで来たんじゃないだろう？
that you came all this way, right?
声を枯らして燃える花のように
Like a flower burning until its voice goes hoarse,
闇間を照らしたら
if you illuminate the darkness,
曖昧すぎる世界も 譜面にして
even this too-vague world can be turned into a score.
夜を数えて 朝を描くような
Counting the nights, as if painting the morning,
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
sound a vivid note.
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regret,
どんなに高い限界も
no matter how high the limit,
掻き消して残響
drown it out and reverberate.
はーい！
Hi!
やりきったー！
We did it!
すごーい！
Amazing!
一番完成度高かった気がする！
I feel like that was our best performance yet!
はい、ということで！
Yes, so with that!
ダスピデでしたー！イェーイ！
That was 'Dasupide'! Yay!
イェーイ！
Yay!
3人で踊るのは、なんと半年ぶりということで...
It's been six months since the three of us danced together...
そうだよね。
That's right.
生放送の時以来？
Since that live stream?
今回もちょっとかっこいい感じにしてみたんですけど、どうだったでしょうか？
We tried to make it look a bit cool this time too, how was it?
疲れてるねw
You're exhausted lol
めちゃ疲れてるw
Really exhausted lol
ゼェゼェ言ってますけど...
I'm panting, but...
緊張感めちゃ半端なかったわ！
The tension was incredible!
もうね、あの、何テイクも繰り返しましたけど...
Well, you know, we did many takes...
本当に、本当に...
Seriously, seriously...
汗だくだよな。
We're dripping with sweat.
順番にミスっていきましたw
We messed up in turns lol
そうそうw
Yeah, true lol
やっとやりきった！
Finally finished it!
イェーイ！最高だ！
Yay! It was great!
しかも！
And!
とりあえずおめでとう！
Anyway, congratulations!
ありがとう！おめでとうでしたけども。
Thank you! It was for the anniversary though.
2周年！早い！
Two years! That was fast!
3年目だよね。
It's the third year.
3年目です！
It's the third year!
これからもよろしくお願いします！
Please keep supporting me!
お願いしまーす。
Please do.
そして！
And!
はい、この「ダスピ」自体もね...
Yes, 'Dasupide' itself...
あと2ヶ月で1周年らしいです。
Apparently, it'll have its 1st anniversary in 2 months.
そうだー！
That's right!
うわー、懐かしい！
Wow, nostalgic!
クリスマスの...
From Christmas...
覚えてるよ！
I remember it!
（歌う）届けて... 切な... あ、できない、忘れたw
(Singing) Deliver... Sadness... Oh, I can't do it, I forgot lol
あれもめっちゃ頑張ったし！
We worked really hard on that too!
そうそう！
Yeah!
あれも頑張った...
We worked hard on that...
あれはね、またしかも生放送だったから、なんか謎の緊張感あってね。
That was a live stream, so there was a strange kind of tension.
そうだね。
True.
今回は成功するまでやりました！
This time, we did it until we succeeded!
やったー！
Yay!
またでも生放送でもやりたいよね！
I want to do it on a live stream again!
やりたい！
I want to!
企画するから来てよね。
I'll plan something, so please come.
練習とかもたくさん付き合ってくれるから大好き！
I love them because they practice with me so much!
イェーイ！
Yay!
しかも今日はね、なんかちょっとお揃いの衣装っぽい感じで...
And today, we're wearing matching-style outfits...
そうそう、みんな上着を...
Yeah, everyone has a jacket...
ジャケット羽織ってて...
Wearing a jacket...
すいちゃんもジャケットだったので。
Suichan had a jacket too.
確かに、スクショ撮ってもらおう！
True, let's have them take screenshots!
スクショ！イェーイ！
Screenshot! Yay!
おい、トワ乗れ！
Hey Towa, get in!
乗ってるよー！
I am in!
ハイ、ブリッコ、ブリッコ、ブリッコ！
Okay, act cute, act cute, act cute!
次は、次はきゅんのポーズ！
Next, next is the Kyun pose!
あ、きゅんのポーズ！
Ah, the Kyun pose!
きゅんして！きゅんして！
Do the Kyun! Do the Kyun!
きゅんのポーズ、きゅんして！
The Kyun pose, do the Kyun!
あ、みんな愛してるわ。
Ah, I love you all.
はい、トワ先輩、きゅーん！
Yes, Towa-senpai, Kyun!
みんな愛してるが欲しいでしょ！
You all want an 'I love you', right!
そうだよね、ねねねの愛してるが欲しいよね！
That's right, you want Nenene's 'I love you', right!
今日だってねねねの2周年なんだから！
Since today is Nenene's 2nd anniversary!
愛してるー！
I love you!
安っ！
So cheap!
ねねの愛してる、安っ！
Nene's 'I love you', so cheap!
二人のも聞けないかなー？
I wonder if we can hear theirs?
聞けない聞けないw
No way, no way lol
私のほうが高値で売れるw
Mine sells for a higher price lol
早く暗転してほしいw
I want the lights to go out fast lol
はい、ということで！
Yes, so with that!
最後の締め言葉は？
What's the closing phrase?
締め言葉、うん。
Closing phrase, yeah.
行きますよ、せーの！
Here we go, one, two!
繋がる、ダスピデ！
Connecting, Dasupide!
イェーイ！
Yay!
バイバーイ！
Bye bye!
小さな手のひら
作詞・作曲 麻枝准
Small Palm
Lyrics & Composition: Jun Maeda
遠くで
In the distance,
揺れてる稲穂の海
The sea of rice ears is swaying
帆上げ
Raising the sail,
目指した想い出へと
Towards the memories I aimed for
僕らは
We...
僕らは 今日までの
We are, up until today,
悲しいこと全部 覚えてるか
Remembering all the sad things?
忘れたか
Have we forgotten?
小さな手のひら
Chiisana Tenohira (Tiny Palm)
小さな手にも
Even in small hands
いつからか僕ら
since when did we
追い越してく強さ
find the strength to overtake?
熟れた葡萄の下
Under the ripe grapes
泣いてた日から
from the day I was crying
歩いた
I walked.
小さな手でも
Even with small hands,
離れても僕らは
even if we are apart, we
この道行くんだ
will go down this path.
いつか来る日は
The day that will come someday,
一番の想い出を
the best of memories
しまって
I'll keep tucked away.
季節は移り
The seasons change,
もう冷たい風が
and already a cold wind...
包まれて眠れ
Sleep, wrapped up in it...
あの春の歌の中で
within that song of spring.
小さな手に
In small hands
いつからか僕ら
since when did we
追い越してく強さ
find the strength to overtake?
濡れた頬には
On wet cheeks
どれだけの笑顔が
how many smiles
映った
were reflected?
小さな手でも
Even with small hands,
離れても僕らは
even if we are apart, we
この道行くんだ
will go down this path.
そして来る日は
And on the day that comes,
僕らも想い出を
we too will have put our memories
しまった
away.
小さな手でも
With these hands,
いつの日か僕ら
someday we
追い越して行くんだ
will overtake and go on.
やがて来る日は
The day that will eventually come
新しい季節を
will have opened up
開いた
a new season.
はい！というわけで、えー
Yes! And with that, uh...
小さな手のひら
"Chiisana Tenohira,"
そしてゲストパート
and the guest part,
見ていただきました！
you've just seen them!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
イェーイ！
Yay!
小さな手のひらね、リクエスト多かったんですね。
"Chiisana Tenohira" was highly requested.
どうでした？
How was it?
お楽しみいただけましたでしょうか？
Did you enjoy it?
も〜〜〜
Mooooo...
そしてゲストパートはいかがでしたか？
And how did you like the guest part?
あの、みんな来てくれてありがとうございました。
Um, thank you everyone for coming.
楽しかったです。
It was fun.
もももわ〜〜〜〜
Momomowa~~~~
いっつも、みんな
Everyone, as always,
みんな可愛くてよかったです。
everyone was so cute and it was great.
また遊んでください。
Please play with me again.
あ、そういえば
Oh, by the way...
みんな気づいちゃった？
did you all notice?
これこれこれこれ！
This, this, this, this!
気づいちゃったかな？
I wonder if you noticed?
これのこいつの存在に...
The existence of this thing...
見て見て！
Look, look!
ヘッドセット！
A headset!
作ってもらいました！
I had it made for me!
ねねのオリジナルのね、だけのヘッドセット。
Nene's original, one-and-only headset.
可愛い！
It's cute!
桃がこうやってキラキラ...
The peach sparkles like this...
ぴしゃぴしゃって！
sparkling away!
可愛いでしょう？
It's cute, isn't it?
この遠目から見たときにも、この圧倒的存在感。
Even from a distance, it has an overwhelming presence.
可愛い！素晴らしい素晴らしい！
Cute! It's wonderful, wonderful!
イェーイ！
Yay!
あ、みんなトレンド1位入れてくれてありがとう！
Ah, thank you everyone for getting us to #1 on trending!
ちょっとサービスしてあげようか。
Shall I give you a little fan service?
どんなのがいい？
What would you like?
今日ね、スカートの調子がいいから。
Today, my skirt is in good condition.
ほら！ら！ら！
There! There! There!
はい、激激サービス。
There, super super fan service.
はぁ〜、疲れた。
Phew, I'm tired.
お水飲みつつ...
Drinking some water...
やばい時間やばい。
Oh no, time is tight.
え？いいじゃん。
Eh? It's fine.
ほら、ほら、ほら、ほら！
There, there, there, there!
よし。じゃあ次の曲行っちゃおうかな。
Alright. Shall we go to the next song?
次の曲もリクエストあった曲なので、
The next song was also requested,
あの、楽しみにしといてくれると嬉しいです。
so I'd be happy if you look forward to it.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
整え... 整え直して...
Getting ready... Fixing myself up...
よし。
Alright.
行きましょう。というわけで、
Let's go. So, with that,
それでは次の曲聞いてください。
please listen to the next song.
バニラソルト！
Vanilla Salt!
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
Burning Love
アマイ
Sweet
バニラソルト
作詞 Satomi 作曲 Funta7
Vanilla Salt
Lyrics: Satomi / Composition: Funta7
アマイだけなら
If it's just sweet
ソルト
Salt
かけましょう
Let's sprinkle some on
誰よりも もっともっと 私を
Because more than anyone else,
知って欲しいから さらけだしたい
I want you to know me more, I want to bare it all
でも出来ないの
But I can't do it
経験Not モドカシすぎる
No experience, it's so frustrating
弱さみせようとすればするほど
The more I try to show my weakness
ムダに強がり すべてがウラハラ
I pointlessly act tough, everything's the opposite
本当は私
Truth is,
泣き虫なんだった 黙ってたけど
I was a crybaby, I kept it a secret though
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But love that's only sweet is a bit
私が求めているモノとは違う
different from what I'm looking for
シロと言われたら
If you say white
クロだって言っちゃう
I'll say black
素直になれない
I can't be honest,
アマノジャク
I'm a contrarian
スキと言われたら
If you say you like me
ダイキライだって
I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのに
Even though I'm happy,
ナニ言ってんだろう？
what am I even saying?
アマイ
Sweet
バニラに
vanilla
ソルト
Salt
かけるように...
Like sprinkling on some salt...
一途にスキになってしまったら
If I fall for you wholeheartedly
24時間 7日間 ずっと
24 hours a day, 7 days a week, always
あなたのこと ひたすらI think
I'm just thinking of you, I think
かなり極端
it's quite extreme
まさかここまであなたにハマると
I never thought I'd fall for you this hard
誰も予想なんてしてなかった
No one could have ever predicted it
天気予報じゃ 当たらないんだ
Even a weather forecast wouldn't get it right
恋の行方は
The direction of love
2人で一緒にいる時間に
In the time we spend together,
刻まれた想い出は
the memories carved into it
タカラモノなんだ
are my treasures
右と言われたら
If you say right
左に曲がっちゃう
I'll turn left
素直になれない
I can't be honest,
アマノジャク
I'm a contrarian
スキと言われたら
If you say you like me
ダイキライだって
I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのに
Even though I'm happy,
ナニ言ってんだろう？
what am I even saying?
Burning Love
アマいだけのバニラより
Rather than just sweet vanilla,
ちょっと塩した方が
adding a little salt
甘みも増してゆくしね
makes it even sweeter
飽きがこない...
and you won't get tired of it...
アマいだけの愛もそう
Love that's only sweet is the same,
ちょっと塩した方が
adding a little salt
2人の距離も縮まり きっと
will bring us closer, and surely
今日より素敵な未来が待ってるの...
a future more wonderful than today awaits...
シロと言われたら
If you say white
クロだって言っちゃう
I'll say black
素直になれない
I can't be honest,
アマノジャク
I'm a contrarian
スキと言われたら
If you say you like me
ダイキライだって
I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのに
Even though I'm happy,
ナニ言ってんだろう？
what am I even saying?
アマイ
Sweet
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
ソルト
Salt
かけましょう
Let's sprinkle some on
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
With vanilla salt...
バニラソルトで
...with vanilla salt.
With vanilla salt...
バニラソルトで
...with vanilla salt.
With vanilla salt...
バニラソルトで
...with vanilla salt.
With vanilla salt...
バニラソルトで
...with vanilla salt.
With vanilla salt...
バニラソルトで
...with vanilla salt.
With vanilla salt...
バニラソルトで
...with vanilla salt.
はい、というわけでバニラソルトお聞きいただきました。
Yes, and so you've just heard "Vanilla Salt."
はぁ... ふぅ...
(Heavy breathing)
どうだった？ どうですか？
How was it? What did you think?
どう、どう、どう？
Well, well, well?
あ、これはみんな、心の綺麗な人にしか見えないお水です。
Ah, this is water that only people
with pure hearts can see.
ねねには見えてるけど、みんなには見えんだろうな。
I can see it, but I bet you guys can't.
あ、鼻水... (すんすん)
Ah, my nose is running... (sniff)
今は大丈夫だよ。なんか今日ちょっと鼻声だよね。
I'm okay now. My voice sounds
a bit nasal today, doesn't it?
鼻詰まってないんだけどね、なんかさらさらするやつが垂れてくるから本当に厄介だわ。
My nose isn't blocked, but something's
dripping, so it's really annoying.
でも今は大丈夫。
But I'm fine now.
はい。えー、さて、サムネにもさ、みんな「いっぱい告知あり」みたいな感じで書いてあったでしょ。
Right. So, you saw how I wrote "lots of
announcements" in the thumbnail, right?
そのうちの一つ目、ひとつめ！ ここで発表します！ (ドゥルルルル...)
The first of those, the first one!
I'll announce it here! (Drumroll...)
重大告知。その１。わー！
Major announcement #1. Yay!
それは、ねねの新しいオリジナルソングが... 出ます！ デン！
It is... Nene's new original song...
is coming out! Tada!
こちら！ うわー、このジャケット、可愛いでしょ。
Here it is! Wow, this cover art is cute, isn't it?
めっちゃいい感じ、エモい顔しちゃって。これみんな読めますか？
It's got a great vibe, with an emotional look.
Can everyone read this?
これね、あの、ちょっとカッコいい英語で書いてあるから、ねねが読んであげます。
It's written in cool-looking English,
so I'll read it for you.
Ring-A-Linger。 リンガリンガーです。
"Ring-A-Linger." It's Ring-A-Linger.
いいでしょ、この響きがいいでしょ。覚えた、みんな？
Isn't it nice? The ring of it is nice,
right? Did everyone get that?
これどんな曲だと思う？ ちょっと待って。
What kind of song do you think it is? Wait a sec.
どんな曲だと思う、みんな？ 聞きたいでしょ？
What kind of song do you think it is,
everyone? You want to hear it, right?
こんなね、息ぜはぜはでも...
Even though I'm out of breath like this...
ひと、一溜まりお水を飲めば... (げほっ)
If I just take a gulp of water... (cough)
え、どんな曲、どっち系だと思う？ 静か系だと思う？ 元気系だと思う？
What kind of song, which type do you think?
A quiet one? Or a high-energy one?
今、あのね、こちら、今回もヒゲドライバーさんが作ってくれたんですけど。
Well, this one was also made
by Hige Driver-san.
今回ちょっとね、今までのねねの雰囲気とは、ちょっと違う感じなんじゃないかなーって思ってるんですけど。
I think it has a bit of a different feel
from my previous songs, though.
ちょっと聞いてもらおうかなー、じゃあみんなに。
I think I'll let you all hear it then.
まずいよ、これが一番ねね、あの、まずいから。
This is bad, this is what I'm most... worried about.
緊張しちゃうんでこれ難しいんだよ、これめっちゃ難しいから。
I'm getting nervous because this is hard,
it's really difficult.
ちょっと待って、間違えちゃってもでもみんな分かんないから、初回だから。
Wait a sec, even if I make a mistake,
you won't know since it's the first time.
いや、行ってみますか、じゃ。というわけで、それでは、聞いてください。
Alright, shall we go then? So,
without further ado, please listen.
桃鈴ねね、新しいオリジナルソング、Ring-A-Linger。
Momosuzu Nene, new original song,
"Ring-A-Linger."
Ring-A-Linger
作詞・作曲 ヒゲドライバー
Lyrics/Composition: Hige Driver
空、空、いつの間に暗くなってさ
The sky, the sky, it's grown dark
before I knew it
音、音、寂しくないよう包んで
Sounds, sounds, wrap around me
so I'm not lonely
時間、時間、黙っていても去っていくなら
Time, time, if it passes even in silence
夢、夢、追いかけるよう踏み出すステップ
Dreams, dreams, stepping out as if
to chase them
悩みもすぐに書き消すくらい...
So much that it wipes away
my worries instantly...
響いていく音
The sounds ringing out...
The sound that resonates
Ring-A-Linger カラダは
Ring-A-Linger, my body...
透明なビート感じて
feels the transparent beat
自然と動き出している
and starts moving naturally
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look
Ring-A-Linger ココロは
Ring-A-Linger, my heart...
キミのココロと共鳴して
resonates with your heart
喜びの鈴が鳴る
and the bells of joy ring
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look
踊ろう 踊ろう 踊ろう
Let's dance, let's dance, let's dance
花、花
Flower, flower
真っ直ぐ生きていたいけど
I want to live my life straight, but...
風、風
Wind, wind
背伸びするほど強くて
is so strong it makes me stand on my toes
未来、未来
Future, future
上手く予想できないけど
I can't predict it very well, but...
自問自答
Self-questioning and answering
するように繰り返すムーヴ
repeating the moves like I'm doing that
同じリズムで、
In the same rhythm,
キミとわたし
you and I
鼓動重ねたら、さぁ
When our heartbeats overlap, come on!
Ring-A-Linger 大丈夫
Ring-A-Linger, it's okay
今はもう迷うことはない
I have no more doubts now
メロディーの示すほうへ
Towards where the melody leads
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look
Ring-A-Linger 涙も
Ring-A-Linger, even tears
汗も生きている証なら
and sweat are proof of being alive
ここにいるって声上げよう
so let's raise our voices and say we're here
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look
真っ暗な夜が
A pitch-black night
来て
comes
見えなくなってしまう前に
before it becomes invisible
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more
Ring-A-Linger カラダは
Ring-A-Linger, my body...
透明なビート感じて
feels the transparent beat
自然と動き出している
and starts moving naturally
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look
Ring-A-Linger ココロは
Ring-A-Linger, my heart...
キミのココロと共鳴して
resonates with your heart
喜びの鈴が鳴る
and the bells of joy ring
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look
踊ろう 踊ろう 踊ろう
Let's dance, let's dance, let's dance
はーい！というわけでいかがでしたでしょうか？
Alright! So, how was it?
新しい曲「Ring-A-Linger」でした！
That was my new song, "Ring-A-Linger"!
はい、はい、めっちゃ(息切れ)
Yes, yes, I'm so... [out of breath]
これ、これ、ダンスのカロリーが高いぜ。
This, this dance burns a lot of calories.
そして、えー、この…ちょっと待って、はい。
And, uh, this... hold on, yes.
この「Ring-A-Linger」なんですけれども、
About this "Ring-A-Linger" song,
この後22時15分からなんとフル尺の
at 10:15 PM later, surprisingly, the full-length
3Dの完全版のMVがプレミア公開されます！
3D complete version MV will have its premiere!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ちょっとね、今ね、息の乱れで、あのボコボコだった音程を、
Since my breathing is a bit off right now, those shaky pitches...
MVで綺麗に綺麗に綺麗に綺麗になってますので、
have been made perfectly, perfectly, perfectly clean in the MV,
あの、よかったらね、一緒にプレミア公開見ましょう。
so if you'd like, let's watch the premiere together.
ねねも行きます。
Nene will be there too.
そしてこの楽曲は、
And this song,
この後の0時からですね、24時の、なりたての時間から、
from 12:00 AM later, well, right after it turns 12:00 AM,
各音楽サイトで配信されますので皆様よかったら
will be available on various music sites, so everyone, if you'd like,
これからのね、あの活動のためにも、いっぱい聴いてくれると嬉しいです。
for my future activities too, I'd be happy if you listen to it a lot.
さらにさらに重大発表その2！
And furthermore, major announcement number two!
なんと「Ring-A-Linger」のタイアップ決まりました！
Believe it or not, a tie-up for "Ring-A-Linger" has been decided!
こちら！
This one!
はい、なんと読売テレビさん、そして日本テレビさんで
Yes, surprisingly, on Yomiuri TV and Nippon TV,
放送中の...
currently broadcasting...
桃鈴ねね × マンガ沼 タイアップ決定！ 「川島・山内のマンガ沼」 11-12月エンディングテーマ
Momosuzu Nene x Manga-numa Tie-up Decided! "Kawashima & Yamauchi's Manga-numa" Nov-Dec Ending Theme
「川島・山内のマンガ沼」という番組のエンディングテーマになりました！イエーイ！
It's been chosen as the ending theme for the show "Kawashima/Yamauchi's Manga Numa"! Yay!
ふー！ふー！ふー！ふー！ふー！ふー！ふー！ふー！
Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo!
放送日とか時間帯の詳細は、このあとホロライブミュージックのTwitterから詳細が出ますので...
Details regarding broadcast dates and times will be announced on the Hololive Music Twitter account soon...
...そちらを見てください。
...so please check it out there.
見てねー！
Be sure to watch!
ワーイ！エンディングでねねの歌聞けるのすごい！
Yay! It's so cool that Nene's song will play during the ending!
イエーイ！イエーイ！ブーンブーンブーン！ムムムムムム...
Yay! Yay! Vroom vroom vroom! Mmm...
というわけで、2周年ライブ、ここまでお楽しみいただけましたでしょうか？
And so, have you enjoyed the 2nd anniversary live so far?
これみんな、ツイートいっぱいしていっぱい撮ってねー！
Everyone, please tweet a lot and take lots of photos!
このあとアンコールが絶対にありますので！皆さん、よければ...
There will definitely be an encore after this! Everyone, if you'd like...
...ここで終わっちゃうかもしれないんですけど、絶対にアンコールがあるので！
...it might seem like it's ending here, but I promise there's an encore!
絶対にまだ告知してないことがあるので！皆さん、このあとアンコールコールして、お利口に待っててください。いいですか？
I definitely have things I haven't announced yet! So, please do the encore call and wait nicely. Okay?
できる？みんな。アンコールだよ。
Can you do it? Everyone. It's time for the encore.
よし、じゃあみんな！というわけで、見に来てくれてありがとうねー！
Alright then, everyone! Thanks for coming to watch!
ア、ア、アンコール...
A, a, encore...
アンコール！アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
ワー！
Wah!
みんなアンコールありがとう！
Thanks for the encore, everyone!
絶対にあるアンコールありがとう！このあとラスト1曲やらせていただきたいと思うのですが...
Thanks for the "definitely happening" encore! I'd like to perform one last song, but...
...その前にねねから、おーしーらーせーあーるーよー！告知があるよ！
...before that, I have an announcement! I've got news!
はい、こちら！
Here it is!
桃鈴ねね、2周年記念！のグッズが出ます！イエーイ！待ってた？イエーイ！
Momosuzu Nene 2nd Anniversary! We're releasing merchandise! Yay! Were you waiting? Yay!
ワー！可愛いな！ちょっとみんな、よく見て。
Wow! So cute! Everyone, take a good look.
何のグッズがあるんだって？みんな、よく見てよく見て. こちら！
What kind of merch is there? Everyone, look closely. This!
なんと桃鈴ねね、1st EP、CD！「ねねねのね！」発売！イエーイ！
Momosuzu Nene's 1st EP CD, "Neneneno Ne!" is being released! Yay!
ねっこも喜んでる！
The Nekkons are happy too!
やばい！みんな、ねね、今までのねねの曲プラス4曲目はなんと...
Amazing! Everyone, the 4th track along with my previous songs is...
...CDを買った人が一番最初に聞ける、ビッグな曲！
...a huge track that those who buy the CD will hear first!
なんとねねが作詞をして、気持ちを込めたんだとか！なんだとか！
I even wrote the lyrics and poured my heart into it! Or so they say!
これやばい！ぜひ聞いてください。そして今回のRing-A-Lingerが入って全5曲！
This is big! Please listen to it. Including "Ring-A-Linger", there are 5 tracks!
ヒゲドライバーさんでいっぱいの、桃鈴ねね 1st EP、発売！
Momosuzu Nene's 1st EP, filled with Hige Driver's work, is on sale!
そしてこちら、B2タペストリー！はい、これね...
And here's the B2 tapestry! Yes, this one...
...8月に発表する予定だったんで、思いっきり水着になっちゃいました！
...was meant for an August reveal, so I'm in a swimsuit!
ちょっと今寒いかもしれないけど、それでもそんな寒さを吹き飛ばすくらい、あまりにもねねがえち過ぎて...
It might be cold now, but I'm so sexy it'll blow the cold away...
...みんなの目が取れてしまいます。
...and your eyes will pop out.
大人っぽい水着を着てお写真撮ってもらいました。こんな感じでね。素晴らしい！とっても可愛くしていただきました。
I had photos taken in a mature swimsuit. Like this. Wonderful! They made me look so cute.
そして次、履けるタイプのごぼうねっこスリッパ！これね、めっちゃ可愛いから。
Next, the wearable Gobo Nekkon slippers! These are so cute.
すごいでかくて、もうギシギシドンドンドドドドーンって感じで、履き潰すタイプのねっこでございます。
They're huge, like "creak-creak, thump-thump", the kind of Nekkon you wear out.
踏まれたい人、自分で自分のことを踏んでください。可愛いね！
If you want to be stepped on, please step on yourselves. Cute, right?
そして次、これ被れるタイプのねっこです！身につけるものが好き過ぎる、ねね。
Next, this is a Nekkon you can wear! I love wearable things way too much.
これは、あれ、テーマパークみたいにね、
This is, you know, like at a theme park,
頭にギャン！そしてピシッと止めるタイプの被り物です、これね。
it's a headpiece you put on your head like 'bam' and fasten snug.
大きかったからね、あの男の人でもいけると思います。
It's quite large, so I think even men can wear it.
これからね、寒いので、頭ちょっと涼しいなって思う人どうですか？
It's getting cold now, so how about it for those who feel a bit chilly?
いいでしょう、これめっちゃ可愛かった。
Isn't it great? This was really cute.
大きい、結構これくらいある。
It's big, about this much.
あ、ちょっと盛ったかも、これくらい。
Ah, maybe I exaggerated a bit, about this much.
え、めっちゃ可愛いから、これはあの、被り尽くすタイプのネッコなんで、
Eh, it's so cute. Since it's a 'Nekko' meant to be worn all the time,
被りたい方買ってください。
please buy it if you want to wear it.
いいよ、これで会社行っていいよ。学校も、お家も。
It's fine, you can wear this to work. Or school, or at home.
なんかね、あの、いいんじゃない？次からねねの放送見るときはこれ被ってきてください。
Isn't it nice? Please wear this next time you watch Nene's stream.
そして、えー、これフルセットの内容になるんですけど、
And, so, this is the content of the full set,
今回ボイスがですね、皆さんからリクエストあったシステムボイスになってます。
but the voices this time are the system voices everyone requested.
みんなのPCのね、あの操作音をねねがビシッと指摘してやりますので、
Nene will sharply point out your PC's operation sounds,
こちらのシステムボイスで楽しんでください！
so please enjoy these system voices!
そして、えー、フルセット購入特典、チェキ風ブロマイドカード！
And, the full set purchase bonus, a Cheki-style bromide card!
ねねのあの水着の、あの、お写真、チェキになりまして。
That photo of Nene in a swimsuit has become a Cheki.
こちらよかったらフルセット購入特典です。
If you'd like, this is the full set purchase bonus.
そして、ご、ごびじゃなくて、あー、ちょっとネタバレになっちゃった。
And, not 'gobi', ah, I spoiled it a bit.
特典ボイスが記念で付きますので、よかったらそっちも聞いてください！
A bonus voice is included as a memorial, so please listen to that too!
はい、というわけで、たくさん告知しました。
Alright, so I've made a lot of announcements.
よし、ちょっとやばい、時間やばい、ごめんなさい！
Okay, wait, time is tight, I'm sorry!
時間ごめんなさいなんですけど、最後に1曲だけやらさせてください。
I'm sorry about the time, but let me do just one last song.
お水、お水も飲んで。
Drink some water, drink some water too.
特報
Special News
2023年1月14日(土)
Saturday, January 14, 2023
都内某所
Somewhere in Tokyo
ファンミーティング 開催決定！
Fan Meeting Confirmed!
何だ？
What's this?
あ、ちょっと待って、最初よく見えなかったんだけど。
Ah, wait, I couldn't see well at first.
えー！みんな！は！は！
Ehh! Everyone! Ha! Ha!
え、何これ、何これ？え、え、え、え、え、え、えー！
Eh, what's this, what's this? Eh, eh... Ehh!
あ、え、嘘！ま、ま、マジか！
Ah, eh, no way! For... for real?!
えー！桃鈴ねね 1st EP 「ねねねねね！」 発売記念ファンミーティング
Ehh! Momosuzu Nene's 1st EP "Nenenenene!" Release Commemoration Fan Meeting
「ねねわかいぎ！」 を開催することになりましたー！
"Nene-wa-Kaigi!" is going to be held!
イエーイ！やったー！
Yay! I did it!
わー、日程がなんと2023年1月14日、来年！
Wow, the date is actually January 14, 2023, next year!
来年のお正月すぎたあたりの土曜日。
Saturday, around after New Year's next year.
場所は東京都内某所。トークショーとサイン会とミニライブを予定しています！だって。
Location is in Tokyo. A talk show, signing, and mini-live are planned!
えーやった！有観客じゃん。有観客！やったー！
Ehh, yay! It's an in-person event. In-person! Yay!
1月14日皆さん開けておいてください、お願いします。
Everyone, please keep January 14 free, please.
まだ間に合うやろ、休み取ってくれ。
It's still in time, right? Take a day off.
応募方法はグッズの販売ページに書いてあるので、皆さんこちら要チェックでございます。
Application details are on the goods page, so please check it out.
えーマジか！マジか！あーマジか！やったやった。
Ehh, for real! For real! Ah, for real! I did it, I did it.
はー、みんな喜んだ、ねねも喜んだ。
Ha, everyone's happy, Nene's happy too.
この、この熱を持ったまま行こうぜ、みんな！
Let's keep this momentum going, everyone!
それじゃあ最後の曲聴いてください。
Now, please listen to the final song.
モア！ジャンプ！モア！
More! Jump! More!
だからもっと 近づきたいから
So, because I want to get closer,
もっと 声をきかせて
let me hear your voice more.
その手 掴んだら
Once I grab that hand,
はなさないから
I'll never let go.
せーのでもっともっと ジャンプ！ (ハイ！)
One, two... jump more and more! (Hi!)
まだ最初は 消えちゃいそうな 想いから
From feelings that seemed they might fade at first,
気づいたら 動きだした ストーリー
I realized a story had begun to move.
123ハイ！
1, 2, 3, Hi!
ひとりじゃ 届きそうもない場所
A place that seemed unreachable alone,
今はもう 夢じゃない あなたがいるから
is no longer a dream because you are here.
ホップ ステップ ジャンプ ハイ！
Hop, Step, Jump, Hi!
未来でも 世界でも 未知に
In the future, in the world, in the unknown,
満ち足りなくなっても
even if it's not enough,
そんなの 飛び越えて！
just leap over all that!
だからもっと 近づきたいから
So, because I want to get closer,
もっと もっと
More, more
声をきかせて
Let me hear your voice
今鳴ったハートのビートが
The heartbeat that just sounded
とめられない とめたくない
Can't stop, don't want to stop
ない！ない！
No! No!
もっと アイをしたいから
Because I want to love more
もっと 愛をちょーだい
Give me more love
その手掴んだら
Once I grab that hand
はなさないから
I won't let go
モア＆モア 声をもっと！
More & More, more voices!
ジャンプ＆ジャンプ 高く高く！
Jump & Jump, higher and higher!
モア＆モア 愛をもっと！
More & More, more love!
ジャンプ＆ジャンプ こんなもんじゃないぞ！
Jump & Jump, it's not over yet!
ジャンプ！モアモアジャンプ！
Jump! More more Jump!
まだ小さく微かだった声も
The voice that was still small and faint
ちょっとずつ確かに聞こえてきたんだよ
I could definitely hear it bit by bit
1, 2, 3, ハイ！
1, 2, 3, Go!
はじめて触れてみてわかったの
I understood it when I first felt it
今でもあなたに届いて欲しいこと
What I still want to reach you now
ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプ！
Hop, Step, Jump!
最初から 最後まで
From the beginning to the end
1秒だって逃さない
I won't miss even a second
これだけは 今だけはね
Just this, just for now
負けたくないの
I don't want to lose
未来でも 世界でも
Even in the future, even in the world
今は変えられる気がするんだ
I feel like I can change things now
どこまで飛べるかな
I wonder how far I can fly
今はちょっと 想いのカケラ
Right now, just a bit of the fragments of my feelings
もうちょっと 足りなくても
Even if it's just a little bit lacking
進みだした夢は
The dream that has started moving
あきらめない やめたくない
I won't give up, I don't want to stop
あのね もっと 愛してくれるなら
You know, if you love me more
もっと アイをあげる！
I'll give you more love!
あなたのハートをずっと
Your heart forever
はなさないから
I won't let go
モア＆モア 声をもっと！
More & More, more voices!
ジャンプ＆ジャンプ 高く高く！
Jump & Jump, higher and higher!
モア＆モア 愛をもっと！
More & More, more love!
ジャンプ＆ジャンプ こんなもんじゃないない！
Jump & Jump, it's not over yet!
モア＆モア 声をもっと！
More & More, more voices!
ジャンプ＆ジャンプ 高く高く！
Jump & Jump, higher and higher!
モア＆モア 愛をもっと！
More & More, more love!
ジャンプ＆ジャンプ こんなもんじゃ ないぞ！
Jump & Jump, it's not over yet!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
あ、ごめん、延びて、ごめんね。
Ah, sorry, it went over time, sorry.
あーーー！！
Ahhh!!
ご、すみませんでしたー！
I- I'm so sorry!
新衣装お披露目とはい告知
New Costume Reveal & High-Important Announcements
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!